Lightning Jack is a comedy, western film directed by Simon Wincer.
Lightning Jack Kane is an Australian outlaw in the wild west.
During a bungled bank robbery he picks up mute Ben Doyle as a hostage.
The two become good friends, with Jack teaching Ben how to
rob banks, while they plan Jack's last heist.
Lightning Jack Kane, played by Paul Hogan.
Lana Castel, played by Beverly D'Angelo.
Ben Doyle, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
U.S. Marshal Dan Kurtz, played by Pat Hingle.
Marcus, played by Richard Riehle.
Mr. Doyle, played by Frank McRae.
Lightning Jack is a 1994 Western comedy film written by and
starring Paul Hogan, as well as Cuba Gooding Jr.
and Beverly D'Angelo.
The tone is lighthearted.